Onee-chan, if you don't wake up...
Onee-chan-
I-It's almost eight?!
I-I'm late! I'm late!
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm off!
Oh, Yui-chan.
Morning!
Huh?
I got it wrong!
From today onward...
I'm a high school student!
TRIPPIN' OUT
You're really noisy
Never ending,
it can't stop!
I can't wait until the bell rings at the end of class
a
Being late is fine
But leaving early is a no-no!
a
I'll study hard after school
My heart won't stop thumping
Going full throttle is suicidal
Hope
Desire
Trouble
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
I'll gather lots of machinery
and I'll program the version n times
I have a photo album without guys,
but there are actually some in it
I'll cut my skirt
by 2 centimeters
and I'll be at the top
Further than yesterday
I'll reach a higher octave than the day before
a
Jumping
out
It's beautiful
Never ending,
I can fly!
Playing live at lunch? Cancel it!
a
Getting
up early
is fine,
but going
to bed early
is a no-no!
a
Fight with all we've got
Hooray!
a
It's splendid
Never ending
It can't stop!
The afternoon teatime is perfect
a
My unrequited love will be defeated
But here I go!
I'll sing for you
a
After school
Welcome to our school!
Please join the tennis club!
Please join the judo club!
Please join the tea club!
Please join the abacus club!
Please!
What are you moaning about, Yui?
Oh, Nodoka-chan!
Actually, I don't know what club I should-
You haven't decided yet?!
We're already two weeks into school!
But, but...
I'm not athletic at all,
and I don't know anything about the liberal arts clubs...
This is how people become NEETs.
If you're not in a club you'll become a NEET?!
Now that I think about it, you've never been in a club, have you?
Damn it!
I feel like I should do something,
but what exactly should I do?
Club Suspended!
Mio!
Ritsu.
Let's go check out clubs!
Check out clubs?
Yeah, the light music club!
But I already decided to join the literature club.
I already put my name on the sign-up sheet.
What are you doing, Ritsu?!
Come on, let's go! Faster, faster!
Wait!
Huh? The club was suspended?
Actually, it is going to be suspended.
The club members all graduated last year.
If four people don't join it by the end of this month, it'll be suspended.
So that's why the music room was empty...
Miss!
Yes, I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, I have to teach a music class next.
Good luck, light music club.
She's a beautiful teacher.
That's not the point.
Please give these printouts to everyone.
The printouts-
Oh, sorry, I was daydreaming!
They're staring at me...
She has no tempo at all.
She's hopeless.
I-I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
She's clumsy.
I guess we can't do anything if it's going to be suspended.
I'm joining the literature-
Since the club is empty, would that make me the club president if I join?
That sounds good.
Um, what is the light music club you were talking about?
Light music club?
What is it?
Light music, as in "light" music.
"Light" music?
Correct, "light" music.
So what's your plan?
I'll wait for club applicants!
You're going to wait?
Yes, wait!
Let's go home.
Um...
I would like to take a look around.
You're joining the light music club?
No, I'm joining the choir...
Do you want to join the light music club?
Um... I'm joining the cho-
We need members!
Please!
You won't regret-
You'll creep her out if you beg like that.
Well, I'm leaving.
Mio!
So your promise back then was fake?!
I'll be the drummer and you'll be the bassist...
You said you've always wanted to make a band.
Didn't we promise?!
On that night when we both went to a live performance...
This is it...
This is it, isn't it?
So those words were all lies?!
Your flashback is a lie.
Really?
This is it! This is it!
Let's go make a band, a band!
You were the one insisting.
You said you'd join, though.
But even so...
When we go pro, we'll split the money 7:3.
Quit dreaming.
You guys seem fun.
I can't play anything other than the keyboard,
but I'll join if it's all right with you two.
Thank you!
Now one more person has joined our club!
You've counted me in already, haven't you?
You are...
My name is Kotobuki Tsumugi.
I'm the drummer, Tainaka Ritsu.
This is the bassist, Akiyama Mio.
Now all we need now is a guitarist!
Yui?
Now that I'm in high school,
I feel like I should do something...
Then do something.
But I don't know what I should do!
Gosh.
Would you like fries with that?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much.
What's up?
This is my first time eating fast food.
Really?!
I've always wanted someone to ask me "Would you like fries with that?"
I'm sorry, let's begin.
All right, let our meeting begin!
We need to get another member before the end of the month.
So what should we...
That's what we're going to discuss.
How about we give something special to those who join?
Give something?
Yeah, like offering something for joining.
Do you mean like a car or a mansion?
Good idea, but that'd be impossible.
What about giving ice cream, or even helping with homework?
But joining the club because of that...
So what should we do?
Even you're losing interest! What about the club?!
Then help me think of something...
I want to go home.
Um, anyway...
One, two...
Poster: Light Music Club - Don't you want to join a band?
There's only one week until the end of April.
No one came at all...
So they'll suspend the club before it even has a band?
I don't want that!
Light music, huh?
Yui-chan, well done!
All right!
Anyway, I'll try joining the light music club!
Oh, what is that club for?
I don't know.
Well, it's "light" music, so I'll just have to do easy things!
Whistling, for example.
It seems like an unmotivated club.
Look, it says you're going to be joining a band.
But I don't know how to play the guitar...
Then what can you play?
C-Castanets.
That suits you...
Look at this.
What is it?
Hello.
You girls have a club applicant.
Here.
That's great, isn't it?
Also, that's a great tea set, but don't forget to clean up when you're done.
Okay!
Yes! Our club won't need to be suspended!
Hirasawa Yui.
It seems like she's an amazing person.
She's a guitarist, isn't she?
I'm looking forward to meeting her.
Yeah! Now we have an extremely skilled club member!
Light music club...
Light music club?
I-I can't get to the light music club if I don't go through here.
Oh.
The light music club is in the music room.
Sign: Music Room
It's here, isn't it?
It's kind of hard for me to say since I just joined,
but I'll tell them I'm quitting.
I wonder what type of people are in the light music club...
You say you want to quit?
Do you think you can just come and go as you want?
I'll kill you!
W-What should I do?
No... No... No...
Oh, the useless clumsy girl without a tempo!
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Could it be that you're Hirasawa Yui-san?
Yes, I am.
The one who wants to join?
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry for thinking badly of you!
You're really good at the guitar, aren't you?!
We've been waiting for you!
It seems like she's got the wrong idea...
Everyone, our club applicant is here!
Really?
Welcome to the light music club!
Welcome!
All right, Mugi, prepare some tea.
Okay.
W-What should I do?
Please try some.
It's good.
It's delicious!
I think I should join after all...
Hirasawa-san, what type of music do you like to play?
Like, what are your favorite bands?
Who's your favorite guitarist?
Um....
I think I should tell them I don't know how to play the guitar.
A-A-A-Actu-
Jimi Hendrix?
No, a-a-actu-
Jimmy Page?
N-N-N-
Jeff Beck?!
Are there really that many guitarists whose names begin with "J"?
I see, so it's Jeff Beck.
Who's that?
There are only two types of rock guitarists:
Jeff Beck and everyone else.
He's a guitarist who's always looking for new sounds and challenges!
You're really cool, Hirasawa-san!
Thank goodness someone like Hirasawa-san joined our club.
If we hadn't gotten another member this week,
this club would've been suspended.
Thank you very much!
It's getting harder and harder for me to say it,
but I think I should say it...
Um...
Um, I'm really sorry,
but I'm here to tell you that I don't want to join after all!
I don't know how to play the guitar,
and I originally thought different instruments were played here...
Then what can you play?
Casta- H-Harmonica!
Oh, I have a harmonica with me.
Have a try.
I'm sorry, I actually don't know how.
But since you wanted to join,
you must be interested in music, right?
Is there another club you want to join?
No, there isn't...
We can't let her escape!
It's for the sake of saving our club.
We have to do anything we can to keep her.
I'm really sorry.
Then-
Wait!
How about another cup of tea?
But...
We have cookies and madeleines too!
Caught her!
It's good...
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to come in and just eat.
It's all right.
Let's have snacks like these every day.
I think we're getting off topic-
Hirasawa-san, what else do you like?
I'm happy as long as it's tasty...
Food, huh?
What do you do in your free time?
Nothing, I guess.
What things do you like?
Cute things, I guess.
Are you afraid of anything?
I'm scared of hot and cold.
In winter, I hide under the heating table,
and in summer, I lie on my bed and do nothing.
This is tough!
What should we do?
I have no idea.
U-Um, then...
Please don't go! I'm begging you!
You can stay here and do nothing if you want!
I'll bring more tasty snacks!
I'm sorry, I applied without taking it seriously...
Now I've given you all so much hope...
How should I apologize?
We're the ones who are sorry.
I'm sorry for trying to force you to stay.
Then at least hear our performance before you leave!
You're going to perform?
Caught her.
One, two, three, four!
How was it?
How should I put it...
I'm at a loss for words...
You guys aren't all that great!
Straight to the point!
But it seems like it's fun!
I'm going to join this club!
Hooray!
Excuse me.
This is to commemorate the birth of the light music club!
That's my camera...
Here I go!
But I'm no good with instruments.
How about I be the manager?
No, this isn't a sports club.
Oh yeah! How about taking this opportunity to learn the guitar?
B-But that sounds hard...
You'll be fine.
We'll do our best to help you with what we can.
That's right...
After hearing your performance, I think I'll be able to do it!
That's great...
So you joined after all?
Well, they insisted...
Seriously?!
You're being their manager, right?
You saying that hurts...
I joined as a real member!
They also said they'll teach me how to play the guitar!
That means you'll have to buy a guitar.
Perhaps they'll lend one to me.
I don't think so.
5000 yen would be enough, right?
Will the light music club be all right after recruiting a girl like her?
Please don't say you're lazy,
because you're actually crazy
The swans are actually
kicking their legs hard
out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
The path ahead looks bright
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
If there's a shortcut,
it's the best route
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
What's important is to take good care of yourself
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
because
you
are
actually
Skilled
hawks
hide their talons
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
Hello! These three are my fellow club members.
I want to be friends with the fun people I meet.
Y-Yui...
All right, let's do it!
Hey, everyone!
This is the first time I've been in a club...
Instrument!
since becoming a high school student!