Kagami Yoshimizu Theater
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!) <3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
The Girl Who Dashes Off
Confined for Two Months
[Princess Confinement]
"I wanted to enslave..."
First Trimester Midterm Results
3rd: Miyuki Takara
Yoshimizu Optometrist
Nurse's Office
Da da dadadada on planet Dada
A robot army to take over the Earth
Fly, fly, Skybill the older brother
Run, Granzel the younger brother
Metal arm scrums against another arm
Sparks of giant galaxies flash
Go, go, jet! Go, go, car!
Space Iron-Men Kyoudain!
Next Episode Preview
Efforts and Results