Lu la lu la
A piano sends its melody to the fields
of dreams all over the world
Believing the broken clock
Whose side is time on?
Why is my heart waiting so eagerly
for someone kind?
Tell me my wonderful future
Moonlight, moonlight sleepin'
Lu la lu la
A girl awakens to the apple of memories
and bestows a kiss
In the book spread open in sorrow
Their bell rings
Because I want to hug the one dear to me
Don't cry anymore, goodbye sadness
The letters on the mysterious door say,
"Fancy hearing cake"
Wonderland!
Welcome, for you...
Fairyland!
It's the magic of love
Love's all way!
Everyday, the fluffy temptation of wheat
Cake for you!
Please eat, tonight...
Tea for you!
Is a tea party of constellations
A chorus of angels at the window
Did you just fancy hearing that?
The voices saying,
"I love you, I love you"
Good morning!
Morning!
Azumanga Daioh
It's Azumanga!
Child High School Student
Whoa! Look at the time!
What the? What happened here?
Oh, what is the deal with this?!
Shoot! I'm late! I'm late!
Miss Yukari, what's the matter?
Oh, I can't believe this!
This is so irritating!
If I'm late on the first day
of the new school year,
that vice principal's gonna give me
a good long earful again.
Miss Yukari.
"Miss Tanizaki, how many times
have you been late now?"
"Keep this up and you'll never set
a good example for the students."
"They're at a very impressionable
age, after all."
Impressionable, my ass. It's so ridiculous.
Unbelievable!
Miss Yukari!
Impressionable, my ass. It's so ridiculous.
Unbelievable!
Miss Yukari!
Oh, man, it's pissing me off
just remembering it!
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn,
damn, damn, damn! Argh!
Miss Yukari...
Miss Yukari, you're going to break it!
What's your problem?! Trying to mess
with me, huh?!
Miss Yukari, you're going to break it!
Take that and that! And that and that!
Come on, Miss Yukari! Miss Yukari!
Miss Yukari!
Oh, the chain just came off.
This'll be easy to fix.
I'm so lucky.
If I'm with a teacher, they won't be
so hard on me for being late.
Hey, Miss Yukari, today's...
My bike!
I made it.
Damn that friggin' chain!
I'll get you for this!
Good morning!
Hi, everyone!
Yukari Tanizaki
Okay, I'm Tanizaki, the homeroom teacher
for Class 3.
If there's anything you don't
understand, just ask me!
Excuse me, Miss Tanizaki...
Oh, no, no. Not that.
My three sizes are a se-c-ret.
But it's not because I don't have a good
figure and I'm embarrassed to say.
I don't mean to brag, but my
measurements are pretty amazing.
Oh, please, look at what
you made me say!
You bold boy!
No, well, your class is next door.
This is Class 4.
Tomo Takino
Tomo
Koyomi Mizuhara
Yomi
Sakaki-san
Miss Sakaki
Kaorin
Okay, starting today, I'm the homeroom
teacher for Class 3.
My name's Tanizaki. Nice to meet you.
Ow, that hurts!
Oh, right.
Moving right along, let me introduce
a transfer student.
This is Chiyo Mihama.
Chiyo Mihama
Chiyo-chan
I'm Chiyo Mihama.
Nice to meet you.
Chiyo-chan is ten years old,
but she's been admitted to high school
because she's very gifted.
Please don't pick on her, just because
she's smart for a brat.
Chiyo-chan, hang in there!
We'll be rooting for you!
Thank you.
Let's cook together, let's cook together.
Now, now, let's see what we've made.
There, it's done!
Let's cook together, let's cook together.
Now, now, let's see what we've made.
There, it's done!
But this isn't cooking at all, is it?
She's a Prodigy
Chihiro
Yes, that's right.
Oh, Chiyo-chan, already
getting help from her?
Technically an English teacher
Oh, Chiyo-chan, already
getting help from her?
Technically an English teacher
Oh, good! Fine! Fantastic!
If there's anything you don't understand,
don't hesitate to ask any of the other
students, okay?
I won't!
The truth is...
The truth is, I was the one getting help!
Am I stupid?
But we are classmates, so...
Okay, time for lunch.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Chiyo-chan, let's have lunch together!
Oh, okay.
We had school lunches
in elementary school,
so it's sort of fun to be
bringing lunch to school.
Really?
But it's tough to get up early
to make lunch.
What?!
She makes her own lunch?!
Before, I only got to bring lunch for
sports fests and nature walks.
And it looks pretty good too!
What is she, Miss Perfect Superwoman?
There, the Double Bridge.
Wow, you're good at everything.
I bet there's nothing you're not good at.
That's not true, there are some things.
Let's see...
Oh! I'm bad at tongue twisters.
Tongue twisters?
I'll give it a try.
Bus gas bast gus, bus gas blast gut,
gas blast gut gut...
Oh, darn it, she's just so cute!
If you didn't do your homework,
raise your hand!
That's it! You're not getting
away with it today!
All right, come up to the front!
You better do your homework from now on!
Yes, Sir.
Uh, well...
I was a little careless and...
I was planning on doing it, but...
I forgot.
Let's cook together, let's cook together.
Now, now, let's see what we've made.
There, it's done!
Let's cook together, let's cook together.
Now, now, let's see what we've made.
There, it's done!
This time, it was a success!
Now, let's all eat togeth...
Oh, you can't eat it yet!
Scary Maybe?
Excuse me.
Day Duty
Did you turn in the questionnaire
on your career preferences?
Day Duty
Oh, sorry. Wait a minute, okay?
Okay.
I'm collecting the questionnaire
on your career preferences.
Here. Thanks.
That leaves...
Excuse me...
Excuse me, I'm collecting the career
preference sheets.
Okay, thank you.
She seems kind of scary.
Veterinarian
Flower Shopkeeper
Stuffed Animal Shopkeeper
Career Preference Questionnaire
#1 Preference
Veterinarian
#2 Preference
Flower Shopkeeper
Career Preference Questionnaire
#1 Preference
Veterinarian
#2 Preference
Flower Shopkeeper
"Veterinarian." "Flower Shopkeeper."
Career Preference Questionnaire
#1 Preference
Veterinarian
#2 Preference
Flower Shopkeeper
"Stuffed Animal Shopkeeper?"
Maybe she's a nice person.
Hey, hey, Miss Sakaki's so cool,
don't you think?
Yup, yup, she's the best!
She's way better than most
of the boys around here!
Yeah, I know! And I love how
she's a woman of few words!
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Just now, just now, I thought...
I thought I saw something really cute...
Bye-bye!
Miss Sakaki.
Miss Sakaki, do you belong to any clubs?
No, I don't.
So, I belong to the Astronomy Club and...
Astronomy Club?
Yes.
We do research on stars, talk about space,
and go out to look at the stars.
If you'd like, would you also...
Would I also?
Oh, no!
If you're not interested in that
sort of thing, it's okay, really!
Please just forget that I said anything!
Goodbye!
I wish she'd invited me.
A cat...
Miss Sakaki.
What happened to your hand?
Oh, this.
I wonder if he was in a bad mood?
I wonder if she got into a fight?
I'm pretty sure it was around here.
It's the cat from this morning!
Oh, he's coming! He's coming towards me!
He looks like he's in
a good mood this time.
I'm Tomo Takino!
Being energetic is the one thing
I'm better at than anybody else!
The wildcat high school girl!
Good morning, everyone!
Yukari-chan's already here!
Which means, I'm late?! Oh, shoot!
As punishment for being late,
I'll go stand out in the hallway!
I don't really care, you know.
Wildcat Tomo-chan!
I've been wanting to give this a try.
In this day and age, you rarely get
sent out to stand in the hallway.
All right, I'm gonna set a record or
something and surprise everyone!
5 Minutes Later
Piece of cake, piece of cake.
10 Minutes Later
Not yet, not yet.
15 Minutes Later
Here it comes, here it comes!
Now, it's starting to feel
like a punishment!
15 Minutes Later
20 Minutes Later
Not gonna lose!
Hey, you there, you're doing pretty good!
Yo, what's your name?
Oh, you got me!
Damn it, just you remember this!
There's water everywhere!
Oh, no! Floor cloth! Towel! Anything!
Someone bring me something!
Oh, Miss Yukari, help me!
Sheesh, she's so noisy.
Ta-da!
Challenging Chiyo-chan in schoolwork!
I don't think that'll be possible.
Okay, Chiyo-chan, do you
know the answer?
Well, no, I don't.
Me!
Okay, Miss Takino.
I don't know, either!
Chiyo-chan, that means we're tied. Yay.
All right! Lunch! Today, it's bread!
I'll have bread!
Well, I'm gonna go buy bread!
Get me one too!
Me too!
Gotcha!
She sure is dependable when it comes
to things like this.
I know what you mean.
Goal!
You bought them already?
That was really fast.
So, what was my time?
I wasn't timing you.
Ta-da!
Challenging Series, Part 2!
Challenging Miss Sakaki in P.E.!
What's this about a series?
You and me, 100 meter race, Miss Sakaki!
Go for it, Miss Sakaki!
Please do your best!
All right, here we go.
Why?
Challenging Miss Sakaki?
But Miss Sakaki is really athletic,
isn't she?
Could Tomo-chan have some secret plan
or trick for winning?
No, I don't think she has anything.
Get set! Ready!
Hold it!
Miss Sakaki, your breasts are eight
centimeters bigger than mine,
so step back eight centimeters!
What's with that?! That's playing dirty!
Eight centimeters...
Okay, here we go for real now!
Ready! Set!
Go!
Oh, Tomo-chan's taken the lead!
It's just a matter of time.
Damn it, I'm not gonna lose!
Goal! Miss Sakaki wins!
Miss Sakaki!
Miss Sakaki, you were amazing!
Here you go.
Thanks.
Are you all right?
A crushing defeat.
Runner up!
I didn't lose! I'm the runner up!
Run-ner up!
Okay. I get it, so let's go back.
Runner up!
Enough!
Then, number two!
Moron!
The Osakan Gal
Well, we're actually getting a new
transfer student today.
The Osakan Gal
What?! Again?!
How old is this one?!
The newest addition to our forces
is an Osakan.
I had a bit of a hard time getting her, though.
An Osakan?!
Tsutenkaku, Takoyaki
Culinary Capital, Osaka
When you think of Osaka...
Tsutenkaku, Takoyaki
Culinary Capital, Osaka
You profittin' there?
Tsutenkaku, Takoyaki
Culinary Capital, Osaka
It's comin' along.
Tsutenkaku, Takoyaki
Culinary Capital, Osaka
It's a rival!
She's probably equipped with some
incredible comebacks!
Yomi, take a dig at me and say,
"Why the heck?"
What?
Come on!
Why the heck?
You think I should make a huge show
of it like that when I respond?
Why the heck?
Ayumu Kasuga
Well then, now that we've cleaned up
all the desks,
I'll introduce you to her.
Miss Kasuga.
Okay, introduce yourself.
Yes, Ma'am.
Ayumu Kasuga
My name is Ayumu Kasuga
and I am from Osaka.
Ayumu Kasuga
Nice to meet you.
No, no.
You don't have to be so considerate
and speak in standard Japanese.
You can just say,
"Darn pleased ta meetcha!"
But, even in Osaka, I...
Go on.
Darn pleased ta meetcha...
Is it true that people in Osaka
cross streets even when the light is red?
Well, I dunno. I don't.
I don't like bustlin' places that much.
You don't seem too much like an Osakan.
I was imagining a more
rowdy kind of person.
It's not like all Osakans are rowdy.
Imposter!
Imposter? I'm an imposter?
You say I'm an imposter, but...
Okay, then show me your lunch!
It'll be crystal clear,
once we take a look at it!
An Osakan's lunch should
have takoyaki in it.
What? But...
Just because I'm from Osaka,
it doesn't mean...
What?!
Why the heck?
All right!
"I was too busy to complete the work."
People often told me back in Osaka that
I was spaced out.
This "too 'adjective' to 'something"
has a negative implication
People often told me back in Osaka that
I was spaced out.
that you were unable to do a task
because you were too "something".
People often told me back in Osaka that
I was spaced out.
that you were unable to do a task
because you were too "something".
But...
I'm thinkin' I should take this transfer
Get it together
as an opportunity to get it together.
Get it together. Get it together.
Get it together.
Miss Kasuga.
Get it together. Get it together.
Get it together.
Miss Kasuga.
Get it together. Get it together.
Miss Kasuga!
Miss Kasuga, were you listening?
Oh, no.
Sheesh, get it together.
Okay, Mr. Ohyama.
Yes, ma'am.
Get it together. Get it together.
Get it together.
Oh, it's time already.
Teacher's done for the day.
Well, adios!
It's finally over.
I'll get it together startin' tomorrow.
Get it together. Get it together.
Osaka! Osaka!
Say, Osaka, do okonomiyaki
meals really exist?
Huh? Osaka?
Yeah, yeah, Kansai people
sure are strange,
eating rice with their okonomiyaki.
Do you do that at home too, Osaka?
Osaka? You mean, me?
Yeah, it's your nickname.
Osaka, because you're from Osaka.
What?
Just like that?
Did you all hear me?! Miss Kasuga's
going to be Osaka from now on!
What?!
Oh, sure.
Okay!
Yes, I understand.
Roger that!
There you have it, it's set.
You're Osaka!
Well, I look forward to having you
as a classmate!
Before I knew it, my nickname
ended up bein' Osaka.
It's like, wah.
Ayumu Kasuga
Osaka
With wings upon your soul
Convey the whispers of your heart
Now, riding the wind
Your soul is beyond the stars
Your wishes will come true, without fail
Come see me, that key is for the future
The voice calling softly by the window
Speaks of love to come and...
Even if the love is still far off
I have faith in tomorrow
I have faith in you
Raspberry heaven
I promised you that you're not alone,
remember, heaven?
Raspberry heaven
Such sweet tears
Smile again in paradise
Raspberry heaven
I've come for you,
the heaven of gentle dreams
Raspberry heaven, I'm coming back to you
On the day the flowers in paradise bloom
You and I...
Let's meet, just the two of us
Next Azumanga Daioh
This is "Azumanga Daioh (Great King
Azumanga)," right?
What's this all of a sudden?
So, where's Prince Azumanga?
The prince is the king's kid, right?
Then, would it be the show that was
airing before we came along?
Wouldn't it be the one after?
It's weird to be calling it Great King
to begin with anyway.
I know! The culprit is right here with us.
What do you mean, "culprit"?
This preview is Prince Azumanga!